Guide to the Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006 AIS.2006.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Personal, 1945-2003; IV.
  - LIfetime Achievement Shine Award, August 2010 (Box 44, Item 8)
  - Talk Magazine Award, undated (Box 44, Item 9)
  - Eastern Star Excellence Award, June 2009 (Box 44, Item 10)
  - Iota Phi Foundation Service Award, November 2013 (Box 44, Item 11)
  - League of Women Voters Good Government Award, 2014 (Box 44, Item 12)
  - CCAC Vanguard Diversity Award, 2010 (Box 44, Item 13)
  - Urban League Lifetime Acheivement Award, December 2012 (Box 45, Item 2)
  - Allegheny County Chief Executive Public Service Award, 2013 (Box 45, Item 3)
  - Drum Major for Justice Award, January 2011 (Box 45, Item 4)
  - Trinity Church Oscar, August 2009 (Box 45, Item 5)
  - Alleghenian's Ltd. Excellence in Leadership, September 2009 (Box 45, Item 6)
- Related Organizations and Events
  - Acheiving Greatness, Inc., 2014 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Alleghenians Ltd., Inc., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Alma Fox, 2006-2008 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - August Wilson Center, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - August Wilson Center, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - August Wilson Center, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - August Wilson Center, 2009-2011 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - August Wilson Center Board of Directors Meeting, November 2006 (Box 41, Item 1)
  - August Wilson Center Board of Directors Meeting, December 2007 (Box 41, Item 2)
  - August Wilson Center Board of Directors Meeting, January 2008 (Box 41, Item 3)
  - August Wilson Center Trouble, 2014 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - August Wilson Center B-PEP Speech, 2014 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - August Wilson Center Scotti Mulert, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Brown v. Board of Education, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Byrd R. Brown, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Cameron McClay, November 2014 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Catherine Baker Knoll, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - CISP, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Election (2008), 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - ICA Financial Oversight Board, March 2005 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Innocence Institute, December 2005 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - George Bush, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Imus, Don, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Jury Pool (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Legislators (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Lou Ransom (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 2007 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Million More Movement, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Million Father March, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Minimum Wage, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Minority Contractors, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 2006-2012 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - New Pittsburgh Courier, 2006-2008 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Election Reform, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Open Government Amendment, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Plan B, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Port Authority (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Regis Darrow Babonis Sr., 2006 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Rosa Parks, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Tutu, Desmond, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - William Anderson, 2006 (Box 41, Item 4)
  - WGBN Radio (Box 41, Item 5)
- Audio-Visual Material and Memorabilia, 1950-2006; V.
  This series contains audio-visual materials and memorabilia reflecting Stevens' involvement in events spanning his career and interests. There are six subseries, arranged by media format. This series includes photographs, compact discs, LPs, memorabilia, VHS tapes and cassette tapes.
  - Photographs, 1950-2006; 1.
    - Duquesne University Event, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Family, 1960s-2000s (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Harper, Lee, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Home Photos, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Jazz Performances, 1990s-2000s (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - NAACP 88th National Convention, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - National Voter Fund, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Portraits, 1950s-2000s (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Group Photo, 1980s (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Various Events, 1970s-2000s (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Washington D.C. Justice Department Trip, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Digital Material, undated; 2.
    - B-PEP Public Service Announcements, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - "What Does Trouble Mean? Nate Smith's Revolution", 2009 (Box 45, Item 7)
    - Tim Stevens: Police Issues, December 2010 (Box 45, Item 8)
    - CEIR Press Conference, May 2013 (Box 45, Item 9)
    - Launching Celebration of CAV 2nd Edition Documents, October 2013 (Box 45, Item 10)
    - Coalition Against Violence International Press Conference, October 2013 (Box 45, Item 11)
    - Tim Stevens and Leonard Johnson III's "Reflections" (Box 45, Item 12)
    - NAACP/Freedom Unlimited Remodeling Celebration, April 2000 (Box 45, Item 13)
    - Tim Stevens: Celebration of Life, August 2009 (Box 45, Item 14)
    - Dr. Goddess Goes to Jail, 2007 (Box 45, Item 15)
  - LPs, undated; 3.
    - "Blue Monday", undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - "Hold on to Your Good Thing", undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - "Sometimes I Wonder", undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Memorabilia, 1990s, undated; 4.
    - The Spirit of Life Award, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Pins, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - African-American History Timeline, 1990s (Box 45, Tube 1)
  - VHS Tapes, 1988-2004; 5.
    - Address, Martin Luther King, Jr. Program, 2004 (Box 28, Tape 1)
    - Black and White Reunion Summit Against Racism, 1999 (Box 28, Tape 2)
    - Budget Hearing, 2002 (Box 28, Tape 3)
    - Freedom Jazz Concert, 2000 (Box 28, Tape 4)
    - Freedom Sunday, 2003 (Box 28, Tape 5)
    - From Darkness to Light: A Candlelight Vigil for Justice, 1999 (Box 28, Tape 6)
    - Hate Crimes Seminar, 1994 (Box 28, Tape 7)
    - His Place, undated (Box 28, Tape 8)
    - Holiday Heritage, 1997 (Box 28, Tape 9)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 1999 (Box 28, Tape 10)
    - Human Rights Dinner, Part 1, 2003 (Box 28, Tape 11)
    - Human Rights Dinner, Part 2, 2003 (Box 28, Tape 12)
    - Human Rights Dinner, Part 3, 2003 (Box 28, Tape 13)
    - Inner City Perceptions, 2004 (Box 29, Tape 1)
    - Installation Service, 2002 (Box 29, Tape 2)
    - Installation Service, undated (Box 29, Tape 3)
    - Jeffrey Manning, undated (Box 29, Tape 4)
    - Ku Klux Klan Protest, undated (Box 29, Tape 5)
    - Kuntu Theatre Spots for B-PEP, 1991 (Box 29, Tape 6)
    - Mumia: Reasonable Doubt, undated (Box 29, Tape 7)
    - NAACP Campaign, 2000 (Box 29, Tape 8)
    - NAACP 85th Anniversary Celebration, 2000 (Box 29, Tape 9)
    - National Urban League News Conference, 1999 (Box 29, Tape 10)
    - Police Procedures, undated (Box 29, Tape 11)
    - Pittsburgh Tomorrow, 1988 (Box 29, Tape 12)
    - President Clinton's Radio Address, undated (Box 30, Tape 1)
    - Pull Over... What To Do, 2003 (Box 30, Tape 2)
    - Racial Profiling, 2001 (Box 30, Tape 3)
    - Racial Slurs, 1996 (Box 30, Tape 4)
    - Shooting of Jerry Jackson Newscast, 1995 (Box 30, Tape 5)
    - Talkin' Pittsburgh, 1988 (Box 30, Tape 6)
    - Towards a New Bretton Woods, 1998 (Box 30, Tape 7)
    - B-PEP II (Box 45, Item 16, Tape 1)
  - Cassettes, 6.
    - Alma Fox, 1998 (Box 45, Tape 1)
    - B-PEP, undated (Box 45, Tape 2)
    - B-PEP Moment, 1994 (Box 45, Tape 3)
    - B-PEP Moment, undated (Box 45, Tape 4)
    - Black and White Reunion Summit Against Racism, 2002 (Box 45, Tape 5)
    - Human Rights Dinner, Part 1, 1996 (Box 45, Tape 6)
    - Human Rights Dinner, Part 2, 1996 (Box 45, Tape 7)
    - Installation Service, 1998 (Box 45, Tape 8)
    - Installation Service, 1999 (Box 45, Tape 9)
    - Jazz Performance, 1995 (Box 45, Tape 10)
    - Jazz Performance, undated (Box 31, Tape 1)
    - Jesse Jackson, undated (Box 31, Tape 2)
    - Jesse Jackson Presidential Candidacy, undated (Box 31, Tape 3)
    - Jim Tarpley, 1996 (Box 31, Tape 4)
    - Judge Manning, 1996 (Box 31, Tape 5)
    - Larry Shannon, 1999 (Box 31, Tape 6)
    - NAACP, Part 1, 1996 (Box 31, Tape 7)
    - NAACP, Part 2, undated (Box 31, Tape 8)
    - NAACP Address, 1995 (Box 31, Tape 9)
    - Radio Shows, undated (Box 31, Tape 10)
    - Song for Jonny, undated (Box 31, Tape 11)
    - Tim Quinn, 2000 (Box 31, Tape 12)
    - Trinity A.M.E. Praise Tape, undated (Box 31, Tape 13)
    - WAMO's Focus, 1987 (Box 31, Tape 14)
    - WYEP, undated (Box 31, Tape 15)
    - "Thinking About Love" and "Got to be Free" (Box 45, Item 1)